Thank you for watching!
I'm eating.
Be delicious!
I hope it tastes good.
Okay, Hime-san, please announce today's project.
Let's go.
Which dish would you like to see?
This time, before we see the cooking skills of the members whose cooking skills are still unknown to us.
The tasting members will choose whose dish they want to eat based on the questions.
After watching the VTR, you must eat that dish!
This is a very exciting cooking project!
The first four people to cook were these four.
The menu that we asked them to make is as follows.
Gratin and spring rolls!
We didn't give them any information before we made them, right?
I'm sure some of them are not very good.
But if you choose them, you have to eat them!
These four were chosen as the tasting members.
only with a question from the representative, Mr. Yamashita.
Can you recognize the members who are likely to make delicious spring rolls and gratins?
Yamashita
What?
Are you watching Pasadora?
It doesn't matter.
Is the room clean?
Yes, it's clean.
I don't know.
Well... if it's clean, it looks like she cooks well.
It's all in order, right?
Whether she does her chores properly or not?
Well, Kaki...
I'm totally different.
Totally different.
I don't like it.
You're so flexible... so beautiful.
I'm already a shape-shifter.
How do you like it?
I have a cat at home, so I don't have a lot of stuff in my room.
So I guess I'm clean.
Yumiki
I'd like to think so.
Yumiki looks bad.
No, only the carpet is dirty.
Dirty carpet is the worst.
Carpet's dirty.
It's all dirty.
Just a little ketchup or something.
Gomate.
Just a little bit.
Inoue is dirty.
He wears a mask depending on the day.
Inoue looks like a garbage dump by day.
I don't like the idea of Inoue being dirty.
After the questioning, here are the four nominees.
Yumiki's popular.
He's got a lot of family.
I hope he helped a lot.
But the fact that there's ketchup on the carpet...
That was a hint.
Even if I don't know what kind of ketchup it is.
I like to eat.
Yamashita is Inoue
I value cleanliness the most.
Everyone else is dirty.
I don't want to eat at someone's house with dirty carpets.
It depends on the degree of it.
You chose Kaki.
It was a process of elimination.
Elimination.
Eliminate what?
Yumiki is afraid of not knowing what to put in
Nagi is a little too young
Mayu-chan feels like she's not what she seems
I said busted.
It's not what it looks like
Let's start with the four spring rolls.
The key is to fry the shredded ingredients and then use the right seasonings and potato starch to make a delicious bean paste.
My sister is really good at making spring rolls and often makes them for me!
Mayu Tamura's spring rolls are ready!
Shiitake mushrooms were definitely in there!
First, she chose the ingredients from memory.
This is the one from now on, right? Which one is it?
Ground meat?
Beef or pork?
I'm not sure, so I'll choose the lighter colored one.
I'm going to use pork, but I'm going to choose ground chicken.
It's a very thin stuffing, right?
It slows you down when you eat it.
I'm going to cut the ingredients with my own hands.
I'm not much of a cook.
I'd prefer something thinner
Don't pick it up.
It's all the same when you eat
After that, I don't care how thin it is, it's all the same when you eat it, so I just cut it as I go.
Is there an order to put them in?
After worrying about the order, I fry them in the order of meat and vegetables.
Are spring rolls fried or raw?
Next is the stomach, which Yamashita has nominated.
You are free to decide what ingredients to put in the spring rolls!
On the stomach, where freedom is a delusion, we chose a little more soybean flour!
And cut carrots into dice.
My mother taught me that carrots take a long time to cook, so you need to add a little water.
Whoa!
I put it in.
I used my mother's shortcut technique to cook the hard-to-cook carrots in the microwave.
Then, I stir-fry the other ingredients in sesame oil.
I wonder if I'm not supposed to separate from the string.
I worry about every little thing after that!
Next is the most popular, Yumiki!
With her many years of experience in making spring rolls, she quickly selects the ingredients for her dish.
Then, the Chinese cabbage was chopped into small pieces.
With a big family, we don't mess around at all with the wisdom of our grandmothers.
The preparation of the bean paste is going on and on!
Next, Yoda chooses the ingredients for the oysters he has nominated
what the heck is this?
what's this?
What the hell?
What the hell is this?
What's this?
I don't know, let's take this.
We'll take what we think we'll need and put it in a colander.
We'll start cooking in a rough style.
I don't know what it is, so let's just chop a lot.
Let's chop and cook a lot!
First, we cut vegetables with nervous hands.
Then, we put the vermicelli into the matching hot water.
How much of this should I put in?
Boil the vermicelli for exactly 15 seconds and take out the crunchy vermicelli!
Back to Tamura, who has started to stir-fry the ingredients.
While stir-frying, I thought of seasoning for the first time.
There is a delicious combination of seasonings, right?
Soy sauce, mirin, sake...
This is Japanese food.
Grozn?
It smells funny.
The color looks like mirin.
I'll call it mirin.
We season it with Tamura's special blend, based on smell and intuition.
Nice aroma!
Then, add potato starch to thicken the sauce.
Finally, we wrap it in a spring roll skin and deep fry it.
How did the Tamura blend taste like?What did the Tamura blend taste like?
I feel like we're running out of time.
Let's worry about that... but here's where we start the seasoning.
We'll start seasoning it.
What should we put in it?
Soy sauce? Mirin?
Oh, no!
After that, he sniffed out what he wanted, and added Tamura's ideal Japanese seasoning and Chinese dashi.
Chinese soup stock was added to complete the seasoning.
Then he added vermicelli, which had been rehydrated in hot water, and stir-fried it some more.
The top of the stomach in the Jikan style skipped the thickening process.
The stir-fried ingredients are placed directly on the skin.
I can't help but feel that it's not very colorful.
For some reason, he left the carrots on the charcoal and wrapped them in the skin!
I wonder how the spring rolls turned out on my anxious and flustered stomach!
Here is where we start seasoning the yubiki.
Japanese soup stock.
Here too, the smell stirs up the Chinese broth, and salt and pepper to taste.
Finally, the trompe l'oeil is also added, and the almost knolls Farmaki is ready!
And now we start seasoning the oysters directly on the cut ingredients.
First, salt and soy sauce are roughly added as usual...
Looks pretty salty!
Is that sesame? It's not sesame.
Sand?
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't know.
You don't put sand in there.
It'll be fine, it'll be fine, it'll be fine.
That's Chinese soup.
Let's put something in it.
I'll put something in it to make it look like Chinese soup.
I don't know.
Baked oysters create a new dimension of seasoning.
Is this potato starch?
Potato starch.
You're right!
A large amount of katakuriko is poured directly into the oyster, making the ingredients into a powdery mess.
Then, the ingredients are turned into a mysterious object and mixed together.
Then, without heating it at all, dump it on the skin...
It's not heated.
I went to the trouble of making it, so I put it all in and stuffed it all in
Then, after adjusting the amount of ingredients to the point where it's almost pointless
I can't wrap it up in one piece, so instead I use two pieces and force it into the oil
Will miracles happen on an oyster fantasy spring day?
They're hard.
Yes, yes, a little of this at a time
You have to mix it in.
Eh, you look like a sissy.
Good.
I think I can handle tomatoes.
Tomatoes over here.
What are you trying to do?
The next dish the four of us will make is gratin. The key is to be able to make a good white sauce with fine milk.
No, it's difficult, difficult. The kid is saying, "Oh, yeah.
Let's start with the gratin of yumiki with no eggplant. I'll do my best.
Can I just use onions? I don't know why he limited the ingredients and chose only onions.
Do you want to add broccoli? I don't want to add broccoli. It's too much trouble to add broccoli.
With a housewife's mindset, she reduces troublesome ingredients as much as possible and adds corn and other ingredients that can be added just by putting them in.
I'll add flour and milk.
It's all right. Let's add chicken.
Can you make white sauce? On a housewife's whim, she adds chicken after all.
And after seasoning with consommé alone, we start making the white sauce.
This is probably the most important part. Because it will harden.
You have to mix it a little bit at a time. It's going to ball up.
That's amazing. That's amazing.
Add more milk and fry it so it doesn't ball up.
But it's okay.
Then add the boiled macaroni and toss it in the sauce.
Finally, sprinkle some cheese and put it in the toaster.
The bow cut was already done. Once again it looked like a no-brainer, but how well did it turn out?
I've never made it before, but I've eaten it, so I'll do my best to get it right.
I choose three kinds of vegetables first from memory.
It's starting to look like curry. Is it the one with fish in it instead of gratin meat?
What should I do?
What are you busy with? I've been in a hurry since a minute ago.
After a knife, I decide on salmon as the main ingredient.
Then, considering how well it cooks, I cut the vegetables into small pieces.
But I'm a little afraid of potatoes, so I decide to use the microwave.
In the sense of worrying about it, I consume hard ingredients in the microwave, as my mother used to do,
In the meantime, I fry onions in olive oil.
At first, I sauteed them and added salt and pepper.
Inoue is worried here, so he also deliberately adds salt to taste.
And Inoue also said that he would make sure to finish the white sauce, which is the key point with milk and flour.
I was worried about the potatoes being cooked.
He's a worrier.
Anyway, I worry a lot. I do a final check of the hardness of the potatoes with a bamboo skewer.
Can it be done, can it be done, can it be done?
If you're going to look that hard, you might as well try another one.
How does this worry-wart gratin, with no hard vegetables, turn out?
It has a certain atmosphere.
Setsuiku takes a look at Tamura's gratin.
There were onions in it.
First, he selects the ingredients with an air of familiarity.
I'm going to cut it.
It's hard!
Then, as usual, he cuts the ingredients with his skill with a knife.
But you know, we have to make a white sauce, don't we?
I know that white sauce is made from milk and potato starch.
So I start to make the sauce with a misunderstanding of flour and potato starch.
I think it's this one... It's really weird.
It's like a sea...
And then we add the chopped ingredients to the pot of nacho nacho.
This is just a different powder, it's totally different
It wasn't like this. It wasn't very sticky.
When the ingredients are cooked, add salt and pepper to taste.
If it was flour, that's a pretty good choice.
Finally, add the macaroni and cheese and put it in the toaster
Necchonecho gratin tastes like...
Next, the persimmons also start with the ingredient selection!
First, we get the ingredients together with an Italian theme.
I don't know why, but I lay out the tomatoes for now!
Next, we cut up the potatoes in a messy way.
Something is coming out!
In the meantime, the potatoes are laid out silently, as if in a ritual.
Then, macaroni is poured over the potatoes with the boiling water.
The new tomatoes are laid out again, and then the millefeuille is formed!
Then the raw chicken meat is cut on a messy cutting board
Again silently, the chicken is decorated on top of the tomatoes!
Then the persimmons are ready to make the white sauce!
It's done!
The person who led the English meeting, Ganko, is in! He's in!
What is in it?
Then, what should I put in it?
First, the milk is mixed with the flour that happened to be in it, and then it's mixed into a mess.
You'll get some kind of weird bread.
I think I can handle tomatoes.
Put the tomatoes in, mix in the tomatoes.
Then we add sugar to sweeten it up.
I'm adding sugar again.
I'm putting a lot of ketchup in there.
I think it should be red.
Pour the sauce over the food without heating it.
Finally, sprinkle some cheese and put it in the toaster!
The result of the red gratin is as follows.
Now that you've seen it, let's see how it turns out!
Mr. Himura, I'm afraid you've made a big mistake.
I guess I hit the jackpot, or maybe I missed the mark...
I'm going to eat it now.
That's right!
Bon appétit!
After this, the shocking dishes were actually eaten!
First, the two of us tasted Umeki's dish, which looked almost flawless.
Bon appétit!
It's so crispy!
Isn't it good?
That's why.
It's delicious.
Tasty? Delicious?
It's really good.It's so good!
Wouldn't it be better to come back for more? Taste
I think it's because I like it light.
Oh, really?
It's delicious.
I'm glad.
Let's try the bratwurst.
It's so good!
Yum!
This is really good!
Maybe I'll open a cafe or something.
That's what I'm thinking.
I'm so happy!
Yamashita tasted the food on his stomach!
He's chomping down on it!
What?
I don't know what he's eating.
Isn't it a spring roll?
But it might be tasty!
It's not a spring roll.
But they're good.
Let's go with gratin.
And you put salmon in it?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Like a white sauce? Is it okay?
It tastes like pasta. It's delicious. It tastes amazing.
I see. I see. I've been trying to make it different.
It's a little off from the correct answer.
Next, Tamura tasted the potato starch gratin himself!
Delicious!
It doesn't harden too much.
I can say whatever I want because I ate it myself.
Finally, a problematic dish!
Yodaga tasted the oysters with the lid on!
It's a spring roll!
Did you get there fast?
It's pretty tasty.
Surprisingly so!
It's hard to eat.
They're all limp and soggy.
The crispiest.
No way!
Next is the gratin.
It's not bad.
What?
Really?
Why do they put tomatoes in gratin?
They like red ones.
I like tomatoes.
Good.
The monsters are at each other's throats.
I see.
Kaki ate a little of his own food just now.
I ate this. It wasn't good at all.
Maybe I'm crazy... but it tasted like the first drop of ketchup.
It's a lot of trout, but... that place... that place... that place... that place...
If I suddenly disappeared from the world that day...
I'm sure you've thought about who would cry for me if I suddenly disappeared from the world that day.
That's about the only reason I'm gone
That's all I wanted to do when I grew up
Oh, dreams are made to be seen twice
Youth is a bitch. Easy to die, easy to wake up.
It's just a transition
What's so important
Though we lose sight of it
But still we dream twice
I think.
Amber Dan
I dream twice.
Someday it's just a blink of an eye
Something very important
Though we lose sight of it
But we still dream twice
Now I can see my dream properly
Subtitle: Kiyoakiyo
Next Episode
Sitarra's fiery theory on the miraculous food
what is this?
I'm Mie Matsuo.
I'll draw lots.
There's a lot of food in here.
Yes, sir.
An impromptu channel subscription song.
What?
Ready?
See you later!
Nogizaka is now streaming! Please subscribe to our channel!
Bye!
Thank you very much!